Gael Greene Magazine Collection 1968-2008 MSS.392
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Magazines
  - December 2, 1996 - November 24, 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 23)
    -4/21/97 v.30 #15 (Salute) F: Decisions, Decisions. Ask Gael p.88
    -4/28/97 v.30 #16 (Drovers Tap Room, Decade) Insatiable: Look Back in Hunger p. 113-4
    -4/28/97 v.30 #16 (Clementine) What's new on your radar? Ask Gael p134/Charles and Laurel Desserts, Ltd. -Shopping p136
    -5/5/97 v.30 #17 (Il Postino, Salute) Insatiable: Excess Marks the Spot. p.89-90
    -5/5/97 v.30 #17 (Balthazar) What's that traffic jam at Spring and Crosby? Ask Gael p. 108 (Fat Boy Saloon) Opening p.111
    -5/19/97 vol 30 #19 (Balthazar) F: A Kiss- Kiss Before Dining. p 72/96
    -5/19/97 vol 30 #19 (Comedy Nation) I need a good laugh. Ask Gael p 89
    -6/2/97 vol 30 #21 (Clementine, The Park), Insatiable: Many Happy Returns, pg 111-112
    -6/2/97 vol30 #21(Mesa City) Ask Gael, What's the latest bulletin on the chili hotline?
    -6/2/97 vol30 #21 City- Meals- On-Wheels- (Happening)- Giant annual cookout Caramba-celebration of Latin cuisine 6/2/97
    -6/9/97 vol 30 #22 (Aja/ Cascabel) Insatiable: Stepping Up to the Plate, pgs 86-87
    -6/9/97 vol 30 #22 (Paradise & Lunch) Ask Gael, "I get hungry at the movies" pg 104
    -6/16/97 vol 30 #23 (Le Cirque 2000), Insatiable: Space Odyssey, pg 57-58
    -6/16/97 vol 30, #23 (Pico Roco-Wild Edibles/Balthazar/Blue Ribbon), " What's the newest taste thrill? "- Ask Gael, pg 80
    -7/7/97 vol 30 #25 (PARIS - L'Ami Louis, Chez Jean, La Régalade, Casa Olympe, Au Bon Accueil, Les Olivades, Le Relais Louis XIII, Shozan, Thai Elephant, Oum El Banine, Buddha Bar, l'Hotel Costes, Taillevent, Guy Savoy) "The Haute Zone" pg 40-44
    -7/7/.97 vol 30 # 25 (Restaurant Alain Ducasse, Paul Minchelli, Louis XV) "Robo-Chef" pgs. 45-46
    -7/7/97 vol 30 # 25 (Monzù) "My Cuisine Vinny" Pgs 60 & 83
    -7/7/97 vol 30 # 25 (Rialto) "I hear there's a baby Balthazar" Ask Gael pg. 78
    -7/14/97 vol 31 # 26 (Molyvos, Pasha) Jolly Good Phyllo pg. 78-79
    -7/14/97 Vol 30 # 26 (Le Mistral) "How can I score a table at Jean-Georges" Ask Gael pg. 98
    -10/20/97 v.30 #40 Insatiable (Tuscan Square) "Club Medici" p.78-79 "Winter" MODE vol 1 #4 Fork Play p 88-p.90 (issue avail. 10/20/97)
    -10/27/97 v. 30 #41 Insatiable (Rest. 147 & Balthazaar) "Hot Copy" p. 132-134
    -10/27/97 v.30 #41 (Velvet) "Is there a cozy corner waiting to be discovered?" Ask Gael p. 152
    -11/3/97 v 30 #42 Insatiable (Sofia Fabulous Grill) "Romper Room" p. 92, contd on p 94
    -11/3/97 v 30 #42 (Picholine) "I want to impress my British kin" Ask Gael p. 112
    -11/10/97 v30 #43 Insatiable (Asia de Cuba) "Wily Chayote" p. 71-72
    -11/10/97 V30 # 43 (Bouterin) "I'm homesick for Provence". Ask Gael. p. 94
    -11-17-97 V30 #44 Insatiable (Cyclo, Annam)"Miss Saigon? p.109-110
    -11/17/97 V30#44 (Da Mario) "Where can I honor the Godfather?" Ask Gael, p116
    -11/24/97 V30 #45 Insatiable (Moomba, Destinee) "It Takes the Village" p.94-96
    -11/24/97 V30 #45 (Windows on the World) "Must I torture my palate for a drop-dead view?" Ask Gael p.118
  - December 8, 1997 - December 28, 1998, 1997-1998 (Box 24)
    -12/8/97 Vol. 30 #47 (Osteria Laguna) "Good food and a little fuss are what I need." Ask Gael p.109
    -12/15/97 Vol. 30 #48 Insatiable FEATURE(Lespinasse, Spartina, Tapika, Screening Room, Lobster Club, Cascabel) Greenhouse Affect p. 82-84
    -12/15/97 Vol. 30 #48 (Black Hound) "I don't have time to make dessert for the gang's potluck feast." Ask Gael p.104
    -1/5/98 Vol 30 # 50 (!2-29-97) Cover Feature (Elaine's, LeCirque, NOBU, Rialto, Chez Es Saada, Balthazar, LeBernardin, Shun Lee Cafe, Cafe Fiorello, Spartina, Union Pacific, Jean Georges, Nougatine, Sofia Fabulous Grill, American Festival Cafe, Honmura An, Lobster Club, Osteria Del Circo, Official All Star Cafe, Comedy Nation, Blue Water Grill, Atlantic, Wall Street Kitchen and Bar, The Wall Street Club, Fresco By Scotto, I Trulli, Bar Pitti, Trattoria Dell'Arte, Campagna, Pierino, Aqua Grill, Clementine, Drovers Tap Room, Molyvos, Monzu, Tuscan Square, Pasha, Moomba, Second Ave Deli, Katz's Delicatessen, Payard, Les Halles, The Lenox Room, Cascabel, Bouley Bakery, The Palm, Morton's of Chicago, Maloney & Porcelli, Rest.222, Inagiku, Fresco, Gotham Bar & Grill, Churrascaria Plataforma, Rainbow Room, Decade, Bistro Latino, Estiatorio Milos, Seagrill's, Carmine's, Virgil's, Soul Cafe, Frico, John's Pizzeria, The Park, Tapika, Red Eye Grill, Christer's, First, Verbena, Bolo, Match Uptown, The Grill Room, Vong, Lespinasse)"Chow Manhattan" page 23-30
    -1/5/98 Vol 30 # 50 (Le Bernardin) "Where can I take my boss the truffle hound?" ASK GAEL p.77
    -1/12/98 Vol. 31 #1 Insatiable (Tennessee Mountain, The Hog Pit) "Hogs and Kisses" pp.51-52
    -1/12/98 Vol, 31 #1 (Wall Street Club) "I want to thank my broker for a bountiful 1997." ASK GAEL p. 70
    -3/30/98 Vol. 31 #12 (Taka) "Why are there almost no women sushi masters?"ASK GAEL p. 90
    -4/6/98 Vol. 31 #13 --30th Anniversary Issue (Hunan) "'69" p. 71
    -4/6/98 Vol. 31 # 13 30th Anniversary Issue (Le Cote Basque) "'73" p. 82
    -4/27/98 Vol. 31 #16 Insatiable- (Joe's...Again) "The Joe of Cooking." p.65-66
    -4/27/98 Vol. 31 #16 (China Club) "Name me a dish that made you whoop with joy." ASK GAEL p. 84
    -5/4/98 Vol. 31 #17 Insatiable-(BONDST) "Holy Mackerel" p. 138-140
    -5/4/98 Vol. 31 #17 (American Park) "I want really good food alfresco." ASK GAEL p.159
    -5/11/98 Vol. 31. #18 Insatiable - (One3) "Eating by Numbers" p.77-78
    -5/11/98 Vol.31 #18 (Mr. K's) "I want truckling and fawning." ASK GAEL p. 98
    -5/18/98 Vol.31 #19 Insatiable: (American Park, Park View) "Trees Chic" pp. 69-70
    -5/18/98 Vol.31 #19 (Merlot) "I hear the Lutece flame glows on West 63rd Street) ASK GAEL p.90
    -5/25/98 Vol. 31 #20 Insatiable: (The Elephant, Mr. K's) "In the Belly of the East" pp 84-88
    -5/25/98 Vol. #31 Iss #20 (Le Solex) "I'm a dealer wooing an artist in Chelsea" ASK GAEL pg 106
    -6/1/98 Vol 31 #21 Insatiable- (Peacock Alley, Jean Lafitte) "Divine Oeuvre-kill" pg 101-2
    -6/1/98 Vol 31 #21 (La Foret) "Is there a cozy little bistro on the Upper (far) East side?"ASK GAEL pg 123.
    -6/8/98 Vol 31 #22 Insatiable (Butterfield 81, Tropica) "Next up at the Plate" pg111-112
    -6/8/98 Vol 31 #22 (Well's Restaurant) "Happening Dinner Dance" pg 129 Ask Gael
    -6/8/98 Vol 31 #22 (NYM Food Hall of Fame) "I want to give my chef-groupie mate a night with Alice Waters." pg 130 ASK GAEL
    -6/15/98 Vol 31 #23 Insatiable (Montrachet) "Morel High Ground" pg 56-7
    -6/15/98 Vol 31 #23 (Osteria del Mezzaluna) "What's new on the Tuscan front?" pg 82 ASK GAEL
    -6/22/98 Vol 31 #24 Insatiable (Blue Ribbon Bakery) "Good in Bread" pg. 63-4
    -6/22/98 Vol. 31 #24 ASK GAEL (An American Place, San Domenico) "What is tried and true and good?" pg 84
    -7/20/98 Vol 31 #27 Insatiable (Jimmy's Bronx Cafe) "Plantain Hollywood" pg. 85-86
    -7/20/98 Vol 31 #27 ASK GAEL (Cena) "I want to impress a jaded publisher at lunch" pg. 104
    -10/19/98 Vol 31 #40 ASK GAEL (Mexicana Mama) "Take me back to Monterey, Mexico" pg 98
    -10/19/98 Vol 31 #40 INSATIABLE (La Fourchette) "Unfinished Symphony" pg 77-78
    -10/19/98 Vol 31 #40 NYM piece (VENICE) "Venice off the menu" pg 46-47
    -10/26/98 Vol. 31 #41 INSATIABLE (Norma's) "The Joy of Excess" pg. 90-92
    -10/26/98 Vol. 31 #41 ASK GAEL (Club Raleigh at the Oaks) "I long for the nights we had sultry songs with our dinner." pg. 114
    -11/2/98 Vol. 31 #42 INSATIABLE (Sushi Rose/BondSt) "Right in Tuna" pg. 130 - 132
    -11/2/98 Vol. 31 # 42 ASK GAEL (Barney Greengrass) "Is nothing sacred?" pg. 160
    -11/9/98 Vol. 31 # 43 INSATIABLE (Lespinasse) "Born Again Christain" pg. 69-70
    -11/9/98 Vol. 31 # 43 ASK GAEL (Yvonne's Jamaican Mobile Restaurant) "I'm in a lunchtime rut." pg. 95
    -11/16/98 Vol. 31 #44 INSATIABLE (Cafe Boulud) "Dressed to Chill." pg. 81-82
    -11/16/98 Vol. 31 #44 ASK GAEL (Goody's) "What's worth a trip to Chinatown these days?" pg. 102
    -11/23/98 Vol. 31 # 45 INSATIABLE (Scarabee) "The Chic of Scarabee." pg. 95-96
    -11/23/98 Vol. 31 # 45 ASK GAEL (Cipriani Wall Street) "Are you picking on dear Mr. Cipriani?" pg. 116
    -11/30/98 Vol. 31 #46 INSATIABLE (City Hall) "We'll Meat Again." pg. 134-136
    -11/30/98 Vol. 31 #46 ASK GAEL (Eleven Madison Park) "What is Danny Meyer up to now?" pg. 159
    -12/7/98 Vol. 31 # 47 INSATIABLE (Rage) "All the Rage." pg. 86-88
    -12/7/98 Vol. 31 # 47 ASK GAEL (Bolivar) "I ask for bread and they tell me to order arepas." pg. 106
    -12/21-28/98 Vol. 31 # 49 INSATIABLE (12/21/98 Madison Park/Gramercy Tavern) "Practice Makes Perfect." pg. 158-161
    -12/21-28/98 Vol. 31 # 49 ASK GAEL (Cafe Habana) "Shake me from my holiday dolor." pg. 202
  - January 4, 1999 - November 15, 1999 (Box 25)
    -1-4-99 Vol 31 #50 (published 12-28-98) (Algonquin Hotel, American Park, An American Place, Aquagrill, Asia de Cuba, Aureole, Avenue, Babbo, Balthazar, Barney Greengrassa, Bar Pitti, Blue Ribbon, Blue Ribbon Bakery & Cafe, Bolivar, Bolo, BondSt, Bop, Bouterin, Brooklyn Diner, Butterfield 81, Cafe Adriana, Cafe Boulud, Cafe Habana, Calle Ocho, Campagna, Campo, Cena, Chianti, Chimichurri Grill, Chola, Churrascaria Plataforma, City Hall, Clementine, Daniel, Drovers Tap Room, Elaine's, The Elephant, Eleven Madison Park, Estiatorio Milos, Felidia, F. Illi Ponte, Four Seasons, Goody's, Gotham, Home, Il Mulino, I Trulli, Java, Jean Georges, Jimmy's Bronx Cafe, Joe's Pub, Judson Grill, Kitchenette, La Foret, La Fourchette, La Grenouille, Le Bernadin, Le Solex, Lespinasse, The Lobster Club, Lot 61, Maldney & Porcelli, Mercer Kitchen, Mesa Grill, Mexicana Mama, Michael Jordan's The Steak House, Montrachet, Moomba, New Green Bo, Next Door Nobu, Nobu, Norma's, Oceana, Ocean Grill, Osteria del Circo, Pasha, Patria, Picholine, Pizza Joint, Pongal, Rage, Rain, Remi, Ruby Foo's, San Pietro, Scarabee, The Screening Room, Sea Grill, Serendipity 3, Shanghai Cuisine, Shun Lee, Shun Lee Palace, Sonora, Sparks Steak House, Spartina, Spazzia, Surya, Sylvia's, Tabaq, Tabla, Tapika, Tenessee Mountain, Totonno's Pizzeria Napolitano, Trattoria dell'Arte, Tropica, 21 Club, Two Two Two, Union Pacific, Union Square Cafe, Virgil's BBQ, Vong, Wells Restaurant) "Where to Eat in 1999" -- pgs 22 through 31
    -4/26/99 Vol. 32 #16 ASK GAEL (Cibi- Cibi)"What have they done to Yellowfingers?" p. 104
    -4/26/99 Vol. 32 #16 INSATIABLE "Double your Pleasure" (Daniel) p.80,82
    -5/3/99 Vol. 32 #17 ASK GAEL (Brasserie Julien and Acacia) "Give me an old-fashioned French bistro sans attitude." p. 152
    -5/3/99 Vol.32 #17 INSATIABLE " Worth Dining For" (The Dining Room on Columbus, Tabla's Bread Bar) p.132,134
    -5/10/99 Vol.32 #18 INSATIABLE "Old Wine, New Money" (Zoë) p. 73-74
    -5/10/99 Vol. 32 #18 ASK GAEL (Maison) "Is there a relapse into the eighties restaurant madness? p. 109
    -5/17/99 Vol. 32 #19 "Whatever happened to American Food?" (Coach House, Wild Blue, City Hall, An American Place, Home, Drover's Tap Room, Pearl's Oyster Bar) p.48-51
    -5/17/99 Vol. 32 #19 OBJECT OF DESIRE (Gotham Bar & Grill) "A Thin Skinned Couple" p. 92
    -5/24/99 Vol. 32 #20 ASK GAEL (Joe's Shanghai) "Can this really be Joe's Shanghai in midtown? p.102
    -5/24/99Vol. 32 #20 INSATIABLE " Have Whisk, Will Travel" (Palladin) p.77-78
    -5/31/99 Vol. 32 #21 INSATIABLE "Cat's Got Her Tongue" (Red Cat) p. 105-106
    -5/31/99 Vol.32 # 21 Ask GAEL "Do I smell something burning at ABC Carpet & Home?" (Colina) p. 129
    -6/14/99 Vol. 32 #23 ASK GAEL "How far will I go for rumored perfection?" ? (Mela) p. 77
    -6/14/99 Vol. 32 #23 INSATIABLE " Wall to Wall Italy" (Colina) p. 57
    -6/21/99 Vol. 32 #24 INSATIABLE "Second Thyme Around"(Cibi-Cibi, Bolivar) p.69
    -6/21/99 Vol. 32 #24 ASK GAEL "Who's rehabbing Times Square dining" (Local) p.91
    -6/28/99 Vol. 32 #25 ASK GAEL "Of all that's new, what's got starch and grand aspirations?" (Cello) p.179
    -6/28/99 Vol. 32 #25 INSATIABLE " Feret at Last" (Acacia, Brasserie Julien, Park Bistro, Maison ) p. 144,146
    -7/12/99 Vol. 32 #26 INSATIABLE "Adagio for Fins" (Cello, Beacon) p.55-56
    -7/12/99 Vol. 32 # 26 ASK GAEL "Are you kidding? Brooklyn Cuisine?" (Fireman's of Brooklyn) p.76
    -10/25/99 Vol. 32 # 41 ASK GAEL "How do you navigate the choppy trattoria seas?" (Lupa) pg. 115
    -10/25/99 Vol. 32 #41 INSATIABLE "The Empire Strikes Back" (Danube) pg. 92-94
    -11/1/99 Vol. 32 #42 ASK GAEL "Do I see light and pulled pork at the end of the tunnel" (Henry's) pg. 156
    -11/1/99 Vol.32 #42 INSATIABLE "Eat to the Beat" (Hush and Oriont) pgs. 126 & 134
    -11/8/99 Vol.32 #43 ASK GAEL "I'm stuck on hold at the Russian Tea Room. Should I bother?" (Russian Tea Room) pg. 111(2 copies)
    -11/8/99 Vol.32 #43 INSATIABLE "Howl" (Lupa) pgs. 75-76.
    -11/15/99 Vol. 32 #44 ASK GAEL "I'm courting a client who eats only fish." (Maritime) pg. 103
    -11/15/99 Vol. 32 #44 INSATIABLE "Gimme Shelter" (Swifty's) pgs. 81-82.
  - November 29, 1999 - November 13, 2000, 1999-2000 (Box 26)
    -11/29/99 Vol. 32 #46 ASK GAEL "I need a gift for the friend who's eaten everything" (William-Sonoma Candy) pg. 186
    -11/29/99 Vol. 32 #46 INSATIABLE "Lift Off" (Atlas & Thalia) pgs. 144 and 146.
    -12/6/99 Vol. 32 #47 ASK GAEL "You rarely risk a bite on the Lower East Side." (71 Clinton Fresh Food) pg. 124
    -12/6/99 Vol. 32 #47 INSATIABLE "Velvet Revolution" (Russian Tea Room) pgs. 102 & 104
    -12/13/99 Vol. 32 #48 ASK GAEL "Is it true "nobody goes to Le Cirque anymore?" (Le Cirque) pg. 113
    -12/13/99 Vol. 32 # 48 INSATIABLE "Take the Fifth" (Jack's Fifth, 71 Clinton Fresh Food) pgs. 80 & 88
    -1/3/00 Vol.32 #50 INSATIABLE "Where to Eat in 2000" (Markt, Pastis, Isla, Guastavino, Swifty's, La Goulue, Lupa, Danube, Russian Tea Room, Cello, Le Bernardin, Gotham Bar and Grill, Brasserie, Kitchenette, Norma's, Fairway Café, Nicole's, Eli's Manhattan, New York Noodle Town, Ping's Seafood, Golden Unicorn, Triple Eight Place, Grand Sichuan International, Rue 57, Morell Wine Bar and Café, Red Cat, Park Bistro, Jack's Fifth, Brasserie Julien, Acacia, C3, Wild Blue, Daniel, Il Cantinori, Cello, Spazzia, Spartina, Lombardi's, Colina, Beacon, Palm West, Sparls Steak House, Angelo and Maxie's, Morton's of Chicago, Maloney & Porcelli, Michael Jordan's Steak House, Tapika, Churrascaria Plataforma, Rain, Café Fiorello's, Ruby Foo's, Jimmy's Uptown, Jimmy's Bronx Café, Pastis, Balthazar, Mercer Kitchen, Indochine, Canteen, Michael's, Elaine's, The Four Seasons, Da Silvano, Il Cantinori, 71 Clinton Fresh Food, Union Pacific, Lespinasse, Bar Pitti, Osteria del Circo, Lupa, Baraonda, Trattpria Dell'Arte, Campagna, Coco Pazzo, Kuruma Zushi, Sushi Zen, Taka, Sugiyama, Honmura An, Pearl Oyster Bar, Rosehil, Fireman's of Brooklyn, Barney Greengrass, Tropica, Oceana, Aquagrill, Blue Water Grill, Daniel, Gotham Bar and Grill, Butterfield 81, Chanterelle, Danube, Sono, Mesa Grill, Christer's, Thalia, Redeye Grill, Palm West, Local, Shun Lee Palace, Le Citque 2000, Cucina & Co., Nobu, Next Door Nobu, Aureole, Bolo, Jo Jo, Jean Georges, Picholine, Gramercy Tavern, BondSt, Shun Lee Palace, Cyclo, Babbo, Patria, Judson Grill, American Park) pg. 37-49 -1/3/00 Vol.33 #1 ASK GAEL "How do you decide which cookbook you want?" (The French Laundry Cookbook, Gluttony: More is More) pg.110
    -1/10/00 Vol. 33 # 2 ASK GAEL "Help! Korean Food is a Mystery to me." (Do Hwa) pg. 73
    -1/10/00 Vol. 33 # 2 INSATIABLE " One Man's Frites" (Pastis) pgs. 51-52
    -4/24/00 Vol. 33 #15 ASK GAEL "What can Texas possibly teach New York about steak?" (Del Frisco's Double Eagle Steak House) pg. 172
    -4/24/00 Vol 33 # 16 "Best Food NY: Constant Craving, Picky Picky section" (Le Bernardin, Ruby Foo's, Shun Lee West) pg. 60
    -5/8/00 Vol. 33 # 18 ASK GAEL: "Steer me away from yet another ooze of chocolate" (Chicama) pg. 111
    -5/8/00 Vol. 33 #18 INSATIABLE: "Make a Fish" (Esca, Avra) pg. 79-80
    -5/29/00 Vol. 33 #21 INSATIABLE "Vine Connoisseur" (Vine & Commune) pg. 115-16
    -5/29/00 Vol.33 #21 ASK GAEL "I definitely believe chocolate is good for me." pg, 136
    -6/26/00 – 7/3/00 Vol. 33 # 25 INSATIABLE: "AZ You Like it" (AZ, Revel) pgs. 154 & 190
    -6/26/00 – 7/3/00 Vol. 33 # 25 ASK GAEL: "Do I have to sacrifice one newborn to get into Ducasse?" (Ducasse @ Essex House) pg. 180
    -7/24/00 Vol. 33 #28 ASK GAEL "How about a meal for $15 you'd be willing to eat?" (Big Nick's Burger & Pizza Joint) Pg. 80
    -7/24/00 Vol. 33 #28 INSATIABLE "Deep Knish" (Shelly's New York & Restaurant Above) Pgs. 57-58
    -7/31/00 Vol.33 #29 ASK GAEL "My mom used to hide the peanut butter." (Tapika) pg. 86
    -7/31/00 Vol.33 #29 ASK GAEL HAMPTON"S EDITION (Chinda's, Espresso, Maidstone Arms, Golden Pear Cafes, Babette's, Estia, Amagansett Farmer's Market, Lobster Roll, Hampton Chutney Co., Cerulean, Nick & Toni's, Palm, Conca d'Oro, Rowdy Hall, Turtle Crossing, Red Bar Brasserie, Tsunami, Della Femina, Harvest, The Independent, 95 School Street, Robert's)
    -8/14/00 Vol. 33 #31 ASK GAEL "I'm seeing an orange blur as I race to Berdorf's" (Brasserie * 1/2 ) Pg. 91
    -8/14/00 Vol. 33 # 31 GOLD PLATE SPECIAL (Alain Ducasse) Pgs. 31-35
    -8/28/00 Vol. 33 # 33 ASK GAEL: "Who's who in the Great Hamptons Cookie Battle?" (Tate's) Pg. 188
    -9/4/00 Vol. 33 #34 ASK GAEL: "Where are the chefs hanging out now?" (Il Buco) Pg. 83
    -9/4/00 Vol. 33 # 34 TASTING: "And Another Thing…" (Phao, Georgica Grill, Old Stove Pub) Pg. 81
  - January 1, 2001 - December 8, 2003, 2001-2003 (Box 27)
    -01/01/01 Vol.33 #50 NEW YORK Where to eat 2001 ASK GAEL, Alain Ducasse at The Essex House; Amy Ruth's Restaurant; An American Place; Artisanal; Atlas; AZ; Babbo; Baldoria; Balthazar; B.B. King's Blues Club and Grill; Beacon; Beppe; Blue Hill Restaurant; Bond Street; Bouley Bakery; Brasserie 81/2; Cafee Fiorello; Cello; Chanterelle; Chazal; Chicama; Chinghalle; Chinoiserie; Commune; Craft; Daniel; Danube; Del Frisco's Double Eagle Steak House; District; The Dining Room; Elaine's. Esca; F & B; First; Fluer de Sel; The Four Season's;Funky Broome; Gotham Bar and Grill; Gramercy Tavern; Heatbeat NY;Hudson Cafeteeria; Jean Georges; Jimmy's Uptown; La Caravelle; Le Bernardin; Le Cirque 2000; Lenox Room; Le Perigord; Lespinasse; Le Zinc; Lotus; Lupa; Mesa Grill; Michael Jordan's The Steakhouse, NYC; Mirchi; Miss Maude's Spoonbread Too; Morton's of Chicago; Mr. Chow; Nobu; One cp.s.;Orsay; Palm West; Park Bistro; Pastis; Peanut Butter & Co.; Pearl Oyster Bar; Picholine; Ping's Seafood; Pipa; Ruby Foo's Dim Sum & Sushi Palace; San Domenico NY; Sandro's; Sea Grill; 71 Clinton Fresh Foods; Shelly's New York; Shun Lee Palace; Spartina; Strip House; Swifty's; Tao; Tapika; Todd English's Olives NY; Triomphe; Tuscan Steak; Two Two Two
    -09/24/01 NYM Vol.34, issue 36, ASK GAEL;"I've got a curtain to catch on the new 42nd street" (Chef Josephine Le Madeleine)P.77
    -01/07/02, NYM, Vol. 34 issue 50, ASK GAEL,"Had any cosmic thrills lately?"(Picholine)P.100
    -6/24/02. NYM, Vol.35, issue 22, ASK GAEL."Has Naples become Manhattan's new Tuscany?" (Il Gattopardo) P.156
    -6/24/02, NYM, Vol.35, issue 22, "The Ice Cream Cometh" feature P.53-57
    -11/11/02 NYM, Vol. 35 issue 39, ASK GAEL, "Tonight was a zero, I need a major treat" (Eleven Madison Park) P.145
    -11/11/02 NYM, Vol. 35 issue 39, FEATURE:"The 2002 Chefs Awards, Hail to the Chefs", P.36-40
    -11/11/02 NYM, Vol. 35 issue 39, FEATURE: "The Taste Race", P. 42-44
    -11/11/02 NYM Vol. 35 issue 39, FEATURE:"Chef Power", P.46, P.48, P.50 contd Page 131
    -12/23-30/02, NYM, Vol. 35 issue 45, ASK GAEL, "Find me a restaurant with zero decibels" (Upstairs at '21) P.153
    -1/6/03, NYM, Vol. 35, issue 46, ASK GAEL, "Our Clan is convening for a special birthday" (Trattoria Dell'Arte) P.88
    -4/7-14/03, NYM,Vol.36, issue 12, ASK GAEL,"Is Capitale an illusion or delusion of grandeur?" P.190 (Capitale)
    -4/7-14/03, NYM, Vol.36 issue 12, "Cooking up a storm"P.68
    -4/7-14/03, NYM, Vol.36 issue 12, FEATURE: Getting Fresh" P.88
    -5/12-19/03, NYM, Vol. Issue 16, ASK GAEL: "My Friend is the fussiest fish person I know" (Pelagos) P.158
    -10/27/03 Vol 36 issue. Feature: "Paris Review" P. 44-45
    -10/27/03 Vol 36 issue 37 ASK GAEL:: "Another Cookbook? Who Needs It? p.104.
    -12/8/03, NYM.Vol.36, issue 43, ASK GAEL, "I need gifts for all my obsessed foodie pals", (Tadaro Bros;DiPalo Fine Foods; Fairway) P.94
    -12/8/03, NYM.Vol36, issue 43,FEATURE "Small Plates" 46-51
  - January 5, 2004 - September 19, 2005, 2004-2005 (Box 28)
    -1/5/04, NYM,Vol.36, issue 46,"ASK GAEL,"Will merry prankster David Burke ever growup?" (DavidBurke & Donatella) P.82
    -3/22-29/04, NYM, Vol, 37, issue 10, ASK GAEL: "Tell me what's really worth a trip to Brooklyn" (Dumont) P.166
    -3/22-29/04, 2004, NYM, Vol.37,issue 10 ,BEST OF NEW YORK "Sea Urchin" (Le Bernardin) P.47
    -6/14/04 NYM, Vol. 37, issue 21, ASK GAEL,"What's that exotic rhythm on Rockefeller Plaza?" (Taj Hotel's Feast of Many Moons) P.150
    -10/25/04, NYM,Vol,37 issue 37, ASK GAEL,"I see your favorite Indian guru's on the move again" (Devi) P.58
    -10/25/04, NYM,Vol, 37 issue 37, "Hanoi, Vietnam" P.72
    -11/1/04 NYM, Vol.37, issue 38. "Everything Guide to Chocolate" Introduction by Gael Greene P.54
    -11/1/04, NYM, Vol 37, issue 38, "Eat, Memory" (Marcella Hazan) P.53
    -11/1/04, NYM, Vol 37, issue 38, ASK GAEL:"I want a little dinner. A great little dinner. Where to?" (Bar Tonno) P.52
    -12/2-/27/04, NYM, Vol 37, issue 45, "Sushi Became the new luxury fetish" (Masa;Megu;Sushi of Gari; JewelBako; Bond Street; Ebiso; Tsuki;) P.80-81
    -3/14/05, NYM, Vol 38, issue 9,"Dream Meals:Jean Georges; Aquavit; LeBernardin;" P.58
    -3/14/05, NYM,Vol 38, issue 9,"Classics:Gotham Bar and Grill" P.62
    -3/14/05 NYM vol. 38 issue 9 "The Best New Restaurant that isn't Masa or Per Se, (Devi) P.60
    -5/2/05, NYM, Vol 38, issue 15, The New Yorker's Guide to the Universe:Sicily, Italy" P.68-69
    -6/27/05, NYM. Vol 38, issue 23,"The Every-Occasion Guide to Splurge Dining" P.29
    -9/19/05, NYM, Vol.38, issue 32, Ask Gael: "Am I awake? I see David Bouley Cooking." (Bouley Bakery) P.58
  - January 9, 2006 - June 16, 2008, 2006-2008 (Box 29)
    -1/9/06 NYM
    -3/6/06, NYM, Vol 39, issue 8 "Men and the Menu" (From her Memoir, a restaurant critic's awakening (with Romatic help from Elvis, Burt Reynolds and Clint Eastwood, and Gilbert Le Coze) P.32-37
    -6/26/06, New York MagazinemVol.39, issue 23, Insatiablegg Critic, Gael Greene, Sfoglia" P.78 P.120
    -12/25/06 thru Jan 1, 2007, New York Magazine, Vol. 39 issue 46, "Insatiable Critic Gael Greene, Klee Brasserie" P.83
    -12/25/06 – 1/1/07, New York Magazine, Vol 39., issue 46 "Dark Night at the Circus" Le Cirque P. 22
    -1/22-29/07, New York Magazine, Vol. 40, issue 3, "Intelligencer, Le Binge" P.10
    -3/12-19/07, New York Magazine, Vol.40, issue 9, "Nothing Wimpy About Them, Brooklyn Diner, Fairway, White Castle" P.78
    -3/12-19/07, New York Magazine, Vol. 40, issue 9, "Novel Thinking, Sfoglia" p.81
    -4/14/09, New York Magazine, Vol. 41, issue 13, "Insatiable Critic, Gael Greene, Madaleine Mae" P.54
- Accretion 2014 - Series I: Magazines
  - March 1982 - October 2010, 1982-2010 (Box 30)
    -March 1982. National Lampoon, vol. 2, no. 44.
    -Summer 1987. Great Escapes. "The Bite Fantastic." Page G8, G22-G25.
    -October 1997. Travel & Leisure, vol. 27, no. 10. "Eating (and enjoying it) in Beijing." Page 190-197.
    -March 1999. Food Arts, vol. 12, no. 2.
    -November 1999. Travel & Leisure, vol. 29, no. 30. "Casual Dining in Venice." Page 40-45.
    -April 2000. Food Arts, vol. 13, no. 3. "Raj-Podge." Page 90-91.